{
    "subject": "Greg_Wise",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Emma_Thompson",
    "human_readable": "Greg Wise is married to Emma Thompson.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9881068468093872,
            "question": "Is Emma Thompson married to Greg Wise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8895318508148193,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Greg Wise and Emma Thompson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8780615329742432,
            "question": "Who is Greg Wise married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6727199554443359,
            "question": "Who is Greg Wise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6239247918128967,
            "question": "What is the name of Greg Wise's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31158360838890076,
            "question": "Is Emma Thompson an actress?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20158271491527557,
            "question": "Name a famous couple who are married."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13220837712287903,
            "question": "Who are some well-known married couples?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08401022851467133,
            "question": "Can you name a celebrity couple?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04926830157637596,
            "question": "Are there any famous couples in the acting world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Greg Wise is married to Emma Thompson.",
            "html": "yago_7735_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a celebrity couple?",
            "html": "yago_7735_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some well-known married couples?",
            "html": "yago_7735_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a famous couple who are married.",
            "html": "yago_7735_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7735_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7735_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7735_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7735_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7735_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7735_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7735_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7735_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7735_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_7735_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Greg Wise is married to Emma Thompson. The documents mention that Greg Wise and Emma Thompson have been married for more than 20 years, they share two children together, and the exact date of their marriage (2003) is also mentioned."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Greg Wise and Emma Thompson have been married since 2003, sharing two children together. Therefore, the triple stating that Greg Wise is married to Emma Thompson is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}